Guide to the Robert Giard Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- February 2005 Acquisition, 1972-2002; 1; 50.06; (270 boxes)
  - Oversize Photographs (16" x 20")
    - Gay and Lesbian Writers
      - Female
        - Villaneuva, Chea, 1988 June (Box 229)
          GLW# 0296
        - Vincenz, Lilli, undated (Box 229)
          GLW# 0204
        - Vogel, Paula, 1999 February (Box 229)
          GLW# 0192a
        - Vogel, Paula, 1999 February (Box 229)
          GLW# 0193
        - Warren, Patricia Nell, 1997 February (Box 230)
          GLW# 0672
        - Warshow, Joyce, 1991 June (Box 230)
          GLW# 0003
        - Weathers, Carolyn, 1989 January (Box 230)
          GLW# 0592
        - Webber, Storme, 1990 May (Box 230)
          GLW# 0465
        - Wells, Jess, 1994 January (Box 230)
          GLW# 0079
        - Wings, Mary, 1994 January (Box 230)
          GLW# 0081
        - Wolverton, Terry, 1989 January (Box 230)
          GLW# 0591a
        - Woo, Merle, 1997 February (Box 230)
          GLW# 0675
        - Woodson, Jacqueline, 1992 June (Box 230)
          GLW# 0053
        - Wren, Jenny, 1989 January (Box 230)
          GLW# 0593
      - Male Group
        - Atkins, Robert and Steven Watson, 1992 August (Box 230)
          GLW# 0048
        - Atkins, Robert and Steven Wilson, 1992 August (Box 230)
          GLW# 0174
        - Bronski, Michael and Walta Borawski, 1987 September (Box 230)
          GLW# 0127
        - Broughton, James and Joel Singer, 1988 December (Box 230)
          GLW# 0554b
        - Brown, Forman with His Cousin Harry, 1989 January (Box 230)
          GLW# 0586
        - Callen, Michael and Richard Dworkin, 1987 September (Box 230)
          GLW# 0103
        - Callen, Michael and Richard Dworkin, 1987 September (Box 230)
          GLW# 0112
        - Corn, Alfred and J.D. McClatchy, 1987 January (Box 230)
          GLW# 0524a
        - Ferro, Robert and Michael Grumley, 1985 November (Box 230)
          GLW# 0352
        - Ferro, Robert and Michael Grumley, 1985 November (Box 230)
          GLW# 0353
        - Ford, Charles Henri with Indra (Tamang), 1989 October (Box 231)
          GLW# 0615
        - Ford, Charles Henri with Indra (Tamang), 1989 October (Box 231)
          GLW# 0616
        - Greene, Harlan and Olin Jolley, 1991 March (Box 231)
          GLW# 0483
        - Harrison, Lou and William Colvig, 1994 January (Box 231)
          GLW# 0087
        - Hay, Harry with John Burnside, 1989 January (Box 231)
          GLW# 0587
        - Hay, Harry with John Burnside, 1989 January (Box 231)
          GLW# 0588
        - Horowitz, Gene and Stan Herman in Hammock, 1986 August (Box 231)
          GLW# 0542
        - Hunter, B. Michael and John Albert Manzon-Santos, 1994 April (Box 231)
          GLW# 0326
        - Langley, Steve and Leonard Green, 1991 March (Box 231)
          GLW# 0475
        - Leavitt, David and Gary Glickman, 1987 February (Box 231)
          GLW# 0535
        - Leavitt, David and Gary Glickman, 1987 February (Box 231)
          GLW# 0536a
        - Leavitt, David and Gary Glickman, 1987 February (Box 231)
          GLW# 0537
        - MACT Newsletter Members, 1990 May (Box 231)
          GLW# 0625d
        - Mass, Lawrence and Arnie Kantrowitz, 1987 April (Box 231)
          GLW# 0148
        - McCauley, Steven and Neil Miller, 1987 July (Box 231)
          GLW# 0110
        - Meredith, William and Richard Harteis, 1993 August (Box 231)
          GLW# 0177
        - Miller, Tim and Douglas Sadownick, 1994 January (Box 231)
          GLW# 0070a
        - Naquin, R. Rip and Marty Greeson, 1992 February (Box 231)
          GLW# 0033
        - Five Members of "Other Countries", 1987 March (Box 231)
          GLW# 0001
        - Patrick, Robert and Bette Bourne at Phoebe's, 1988 September (Box 231)
          GLW# 0315
        - Peters, Robert and David Trachtenberg, 1988 January (Box 232)
          GLW# 0235a
        - Peters, Robert and David Trachtenberg, 1988 January (Box 232)
          GLW# 0236
        - Peters, Robert and David Trachtenberg, 1988 January (Box 232)
          GLW# 0239
        - Pomo Afro Homos, 1994 January (Box 232)
          GLW# 0172
        - Poniewaz, Jeff and Antler, 1993 July (Box 232)
          GLW# 0450
        - RFD Managing Editors, 1991 March (Box 232)
          GLW# 0484
        - Rubin, Mark and Peter Fisher, 1999 May (Box 232)
          GLW# 0201
        - Schwartz, Lloyd and Ralph Hamilton, 1988 July (Box 232)
          GLW# 0311
        - Thompson, Mark and Malcolm Boyd, 1989 January (Box 232)
          GLW# 0583
        - Vawter, Ron and Greg Mehrten-Gay Pride Week, 1992 June (Box 232)
          GLW# 0055
        - Virga, Vincent and James McCourt, 1987 December (Box 232)
          GLW# 0135
      - Female Groups
        - Allison, Dorothy with Alix Layman and Wolf Michael, 1994 (Box 232)
          GLW# 0080
        - The Bloodroot Collective, 1995 June (Box 232)
          GLW# 0647
        - Brown, Beverly and Tee Corinne, 1994 August (Box 232)
          GLW# 0413
        - Castillo, Ana and Cherie Moraga, 1989 (Box 232)
          GLW# 0569a
        - Clarke, Cheryl and Jewelle Gomez, 1987 August (Box 232)
          GLW# 0155
        - Coss, Clare and Blanche W. Cook, 1987 September (Box 232)
          GLW# 0139
        - Cottrelle, Honey Lee and Erica Marcus, undated (Box 232)
          GLW# 0189
        - Forner, Maria Irene with Her Mother, NYC, 1990 February (Box 232)
          GLW# 0626
        - Gittings, Barbara and Kay Tobin, 1991 June (Box 232)
          GLW# 0011
        - Gittings, Barbara and Kay Tobin, 1991 June (Box 233)
          GLW# 0104
        - Grier, Barbara and Donna McBride, 1989 January (Box 233)
          GLW# 0599
        - Hacker, Marilyn and Her Daughter Iva, 1987 September (Box 233)
          GLW# 0138d
        - Hacker, Marilyn and Karyn London, 1995 January (Box 233)
          GLW# 0641
        - Lyon, Phyllis and Del Martin, 1989 January (Box 233)
          GLW# 0570
        - Miller, Isabel with Julie Weber, 1992 August (Box 233)
          GLW# 0165
        - Rich, Cynthia and Barbara Macdonald, 1997 February (Box 233)
          GLW# 0664
        - Romo-Carmona, Mariana Mariana Combing June's Hair (June Chan), 1988 September (Box 233)
          GLW# 0318
        - Seejay, Carol with Staff Members Susan Vuic and Dawn Lundy Martin, 1994 January (Box 233)
          GLW# 0082
        - Segrest, Mab with Barbara and Anne, 1991 March (Box 233)
          GLW# 0494
        - Segrest, Mab with Barbara and Anne, 1991 (Box 233)
          GLW# 0712
        - Warshow, Joyce, Adrienne J. Smith and Barbara Sang, 1991 June (Box 233)
          GLW# 0014
        - Weathers, Carolyn and Jenny Wrenn, 1989 January (Box 233)
          GLW# 0594a
        - Youngblood, Shay and Donna Kate Rushin, 1993 March (Box 233)
          GLW# 0433
      - Mixed male and female groups
        - Ana Castillo and Her Son, undated (Box 233)
          GLW# 0568
        - Minnie Bruce Pratt and Leslie Feinberg, 1993 (Box 233)
          GLW# 0168
        - Dodie Bellamy and Levin Killian, 1989 (Box 233)
          GLW# 0560
        - AMALGM Newsletter, undated (Box 233)
          GLW# 0468
        - B. Harris, F. Philip, N.Lane, undated (Box 233)
          GLW# 0437a
        - D. Klaich, W. Fairey, Jonathan Silin, undated (Box 233)
          GLW# 0210
        - Walker and Paula Jobloner, undated (Box 233)
          GLW# 0663
        - Veneita Porter and John Preston, 1988 (Box 233)
          GLW# 0305
    - Landscapes
      - Urban landscapes (color prints)
        - [untitled], 1978-1984 (Box 234 (Oversize))
          L# 0062
        - [untitled], 1978-1984 (Box 234 (Oversize))
          L# 0063
        - [untitled], 1978-1984 (Box 234 (Oversize))
          L# 0064
        - [untitled], 1978-1984 (Box 234 (Oversize))
          L# 0065
        - [untitled], 1978-1984 (Box 234 (Oversize))
          L# 0066
        - [untitled], 1978-1984 (Box 234 (Oversize))
          L# 0067
      - General landscapes
        - Dark Window, 1977 (Box 235)
          L# 0146
        - Porch Posts, 1976 (Box 235)
          L# 0153
        - Sprinkler, 1977 (Box 235)
          L# 0154a
        - Patio at Dusk, 1976 (Box 235)
          L# 0155b
        - House and Car, 1976 (Box 235)
          L# 0156c
        - Driveway, 1975 (Box 235)
          L# 0157a
        - Patio 1, 1976 (Box 235)
          L# 0158b
        - A View of the Garden, 1976 (Box 235)
          L# 0159c
        - Screened in Porch, 1976 (Box 235)
          L# 0160a
        - Patio 2, 1976 (Box 235)
          L# 0161c
        - California Lawn, 1976 (Box 236)
          L# 0162d
        - Two Car Garage, 1976 (Box 236)
          L# 0163b
        - Cellar Door, 1977 (Box 236)
          L# 0164a
        - White Rock, 1976 (Box 236)
          L# 0165a
        - Grey Pool, 1976 (Box 236)
          L# 0166a
        - Deck, 1977 (Box 236)
          L# 0167a
        - Gable, 1977 (Box 236)
          L# 0168a
        - Side of a House, 1976 (Box 236)
          L# 0169a
        - Pillars, 1977 (Box 236)
          L# 0170a
        - California Sidewalk, 1976 (Box 236)
          L# 0171c
        - Patio Detail, 1976 (Box 237)
          L# 0172e
        - Roof, 1976 (Box 237)
          L# 0173b
        - New Fence, 1977 (Box 237)
          L# 0174b
        - Fence Around a Pool, 1976 (Box 237)
          L# 0175b
        - Porch Columns, 1976 (Box 237)
          L# 0176b
        - Bench, 1977 (Box 237)
          L# 0177d
        - Dark Pool, 1975 (Box 237)
          L# 0178b
        - Walk Way, 1976 (Box 237)
          L# 0180a
        - Bird Feeder, 1976 (Box 237)
          L# 0181a
      - Vegetation
        - (grave of Ella Rosa Burt, beheaded statue), undated (Box 238)
          LV# 0004b
        - (graveyard, stag sculpture), undated (Box 238)
          LV# 0045d
        - (workers with netting), undated (Box 238)
          LV# 0046c
        - (pyramid of dirty snow), undated (Box 238)
          LV# 0047a
        - (snow covered field), undated (Box 238)
          LV# 0048b
        - (snow covered field, lampposts), undated (Box 238)
          LV# 0049b
        - (entrance to church or mausoleum), undated (Box 238)
          LV# 0050e
        - Bare Hedge, 1981 (Box 238)
          LV# 0051
        - End of Hedge, 1981 (Box 238)
          LV# 0052a
        - (crypts), 1984 (Box 238)
          LV# 0053b
        - (large rock with sign), undated (Box 238)
          LV# 0054b
        - Lantern with Ivy, 1978 (Box 238)
          LV# 0055a
        - (draped statue), undated (Box 238)
          LV# 0056c
        - Catalpa, 1981 (Box 238)
          LV# 0057c
        - Tree with Lines - Willow, 1979 (Box 238)
          LV# 0058
        - (street, telephone wires, birds), undated (Box 238)
          LV# 0059c
        - (rock sculpture, wheelbarrow), 1982 (Box 238)
          LV# 0060h
        - (hedge), 1984 (Box 238)
          LV# 0061d
        - Ornamental Trees, 1977 (Box 238)
          LV# 0062c
        - Two Hedges, 1977 (Box 238)
          LV# 0063a
        - (yard sale under pine trees), 1983 (Box 239)
          LV# 0064
        - Horse Chestnut Tree, undated (Box 239)
          LV# 0065c
        - (tree with flowering branches, lawn), 1982 (Box 239)
          LV# 0066d
        - Garden Frames, 1979 (Box 239)
          LV# 0067a
        - Gable, Late Afternoon, 1983 (Box 239)
          LV# 0068b
        - Architectural Ornament, 1977 (Box 239)
          LV# 0069
        - Bench and Tree (Stone Bench, Green River Cemetery), 1984 (Box 239)
          LV# 0070b
        - Patio, Late Afternoon, 1978 (Box 239)
          LV# 0071b
        - Scene at a Nursery, 1981 (Box 239)
          LV# 0072c
        - Privet Hedge with Snowball Bush, 1977 (Box 239)
          LV# 0073
        - Tree with Swing, 1977 (Box 239)
          LV# 0074a
        - (latticed pergola, tree at right), 1979 (Box 239)
          LV# 0075c
        - (latticed pergola), 1979 (Box 239)
          LV# 0076d
        - (white poles in field), 1979 (Box 239)
          LV# 0077b
        - Untrimmed Privet, undated (Box 239)
          LV# 0078d
        - Hedge and Driveway, 1982 (Box 239)
          LV# 0079
        - (field framed by trees), undated (Box 239)
          LV# 0080c
        - (hedge, two trees at right), 1979 (Box 239)
          LV# 0081c
        - Hedge and Tree, 1979 (Box 239)
          LV# 0082
      - The Creeks
        - The Creeks 11 (wall with inverted pyramid inset), 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0083f
        - The Creeks 3, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0084e
        - The Creeks 13, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0085e
        - The Creeks 14, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0086e
        - The Creeks 6, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0087e
        - The Creeks 5, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0088d
        - The Creeks 10, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0089e
        - The Creeks 9, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0090d
        - The Creeks 20, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0091e
        - The Creeks 18, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0092e
        - The Creeks 16, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0093e
        - The Creeks 21, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0094e
        - The Creeks 19, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0095e
        - The Creeks 2, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0096e
        - The Creeks 4, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0097d
        - The Creeks 1, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0098e
        - The Creeks 22, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0099e
        - The Creeks 15, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0100d
        - The Creeks 24, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0101e
        - The Creeks 8, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0102d
        - The Creeks 12, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0103e
        - The Creeks 7, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0104e
        - The Creeks 17, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0105e
        - The Creeks 23, 1991 (Box 240)
          LC# 0106e
      - South Fork Portfolio
        LSF# A set of the portfolio inserts, including the colophon and introduction by Gene Thornton, former critic for the New York Times, is included in the Yale package, however the group of prints listed below does not represent the entire portfolio as a print of the image "Two Deer" is not available.
        - House, 1982 (Box 241)
          LSF# 0107d
        - Windmill, 1981 (Box 241)
          LSF# 0108d
        - Ping Pong Table, 1982 (Box 241)
          LSF# 0109a
        - Hedge and Hillocks, 1981 (Box 241)
          LSF# 0110c
        - Cemetery in April, 1981 (Box 241)
          LSF# 0111b
        - Circles on a Lawn, 1981 (Box 241)
          LSF# 0112d
        - Nymph in a Nursery, 1983 (Box 241)
          LSF# 0113e
        - Steps on a Golf Course, 1981 (Box 241)
          LSF# 0114f
        - Garden Structures: March, 1982 (Box 241)
          LSF# 0115f
          Note: A set of the portfolio inserts, including the colophon and introduction by Gene Thornton, former critic for the New York Times, is included in the Yale package, however the group of prints listed above does not represent the entire portfolio as a print of the image "Two Deer" is not available.
      - Tangle
        - Over the Fence 2, 1980 (Box 241)
          LT# 0001a
        - Over the Fence 1, 1979 (Box 241)
          LT# 0002
        - (weeds in foreground, antenna in background), 1980 (Box 241)
          LT# 0003b
        - (boat behind tangle of tree branches), 1980 (Box 241)
          LT# 0004a
        - (two figures, one with telescope), 1985 (Box 241)
          LT# 0005a
        - Deer In A Tree, 1977 (Box 241)
          LT# 0006a
        - (Statue of Liberty in scaffolding, bird, trees), undated (Box 241)
          LT# 0007b
        - Car Behind a Hedge, 1978 (Box 241)
          LT# 0008a
        - (station wagon behind trees), 1979 (Box 241)
          LT# 0009
        - (trees, ladder, picket fence), 1982 (Box 241)
          LT# 0010a
        - (man in parka behind trees), 1981 (Box 241)
          LT# 0011b
        - Arbor and Tree, 1977 (Box 242)
          LT# 0012a
        - Boy in a Tree, 1979 (Box 242)
          LT# 0013a
        - (trees and old arbor), 1983 (Box 242)
          LT# 0014a
        - Sunburst Lattice, 1979 (Box 242)
          LT# 0015a
        - Trellis, 1980 (Box 242)
          LT# 0016a
        - (trees in foreground, horse and tents in background), undated (Box 242)
          LT# 0017a
        - (man on ladder pruning trees), undated (Box 242)
          LT# 0018a
        - (dog, fence, building, trees), 1980 (Box 242)
          LT# 0019
        - (flowering orchard), 1983 (Box 242)
          LT# 0020a
        - (columns, greenhouse), undated (Box 242)
          LT# 0021a
        - (street, tangled hedge, house), undated (Box 242)
          LT# 0022a
        - Stately Home, 1979 (Box 242)
          LT# 0023a
        - Pagoda in the Woods, 1981 (Box 242)
          LT# 0024a
        - Teepee, 1981 (Box 242)
          LT# 0025a
        - (garden chairs on top of table in woods), 1983 (Box 242)
          LT# 0026a
        - (windmill in woods), 1983 (Box 242)
          LT# 0027a
        - Garden Structures: October, 1981 (Box 242)
          LT# 0028b
        - (field, man in overgrowth), 1984 (Box 242)
          LT# 0029
        - (jumping fences in field), 1980 (Box 242)
          LT# 0030
        - (teeter-totter, house), undated (Box 242)
          LT# 0031b
        - Stars on a Lawn, 1978 (Box 243)
          LT# 0032
        - Rope on a Golf Course, 1982 (Box 243)
          LT# 0033a
        - (dismantled jumping fences), 1980 (Box 243)
          LT# 0034d
        - Lines on a Golf Course, 1979 (Box 243)
          LT# 0035b
        - Mirror in a Driveway, 1979 (Box 243)
          LT# 0036B
        - Bird on a Golf Course, 1979 (Box 243)
          LT# 0037b
        - (pick-up truck), 1983 (Box 243)
          LT# 0038a
        - (building with inflated dome), undated (Box 243)
          LT# 0039a
        - Fence and Lines, 1978 (Box 243)
          LT# 0040
        - (animal topiary in foreground, house in background), undated (Box 243)
          LT# 0041a
        - Landscape with Tents, 1981 (Box 243)
          LT# 0042b
        - Pool, 1979 (Box 243)
          LT# 0043b
      - Dark Series
        - Still Life
          - (glass plate with floral pattern), circa 1990 (Box 243)
            DS# 0001c
          - Photographic Still Life (bottles and miniature tripod), 1989 (Box 243)
            DS# 0002c
          - Still Life with Physique Magazine, 1990 (Box 243)
            DS# 0003e
          - (still life with bottles and rubber rat), circa 1990 (Box 243)
            DS# 0004c
          - Still Life with Fredrick's of Hollywood, 1990 (Box 243)
            DS# 0005e
          - (still life with bottles and flashlight), circa 1990 (Box 243)
            DS# 0006d
          - Football Player, 1987 (Box 243)
            DS# 0007c
          - (Marilyn Monroe puzzle, table fan), circa 1990 (Box 243)
            DS# 0008d
          - Superhero at Montauk, 1990 (Box 244)
            DS# 0009c
          - Crystal - St. John the Divine, NYC, 1985 (Box 244)
            DS# 0010d
          - (big ladder, small ladder), circa 1990 (Box 244)
            DS# 0011d
          - Celestial Globe, 1987 (Box 244)
            DS# 0012i
          - Sliced American, 1991 (Box 244)
            DS# 0013d
          - (Sony television and sex toys), circa 1989 (Box 244)
            DS# 0014
          - (still life with three sex toys touching), circa 1989 (Box 244)
            DS# 0015d
          - Sex Toy, 1989 (Box 244)
            DS# 0016d
          - (still life with three sex toys apart), circa 1989 (Box 244)
            DS# 0017b
          - (still life with smaller sex toy), circa 1989 (Box 244)
            DS# 0018c
          - (still life with one sex toy), circa 1989 (Box 244)
            DS# 0019b
          - (leather pants, sex toy vertical), circa 1989 (Box 244)
            DS# 0020d
          - (leather pants, sex toy diagonal), circa 1989 (Box 244)
            DS# 0021e
        - Landscape
          - (FAO Schwartz, toys sign at left), undated (Box 244)
            DL# 0022a
          - (FAO Schwartz, toys sign at right), undated (Box 244)
            DL# 0023b
          - Old Furnace, 1987 (Box 244)
            DL# 0024d
          - (balcony decorated with plants, banner, head), undated (Box 244)
            DL# 0025e
          - (Barney's Beanery), undated (Box 244)
            DL# 0026e
          - (Art Deco lighting store), undated (Box 244)
            DL# 0027d
          - Grave of Stuart Davis: Green River Cemetery, 1983 (Box 244)
            DL# 0028d
          - Green River Cemetery: Springs, N.Y., 1983 (Box 245)
            DL# 0029c
          - A Dress for Miss Liberty, 1986 (Box 245)
            DL# 0030d
          - (dress for Miss Liberty, bodice and upper skirt), 1986 (Box 245)
            DL# 0031b
          - (Venice, stone stairway), undated (Box 245)
            DL# 0032d
          - (reflection, palm tree and truck), undated (Box 245)
            DL# 0033d
          - TV with Empire State Building, 1986 (Box 245)
            DL# 0034i
          - (street vendor), undated (Box 245)
            DL# 0035c
          - (fishing net in field), 1978 (Box 245)
            DL# 0036
          - (Central Park, performance art), undated (Box 245)
            DL# 0037c
          - (Planetarium exterior, New York City), undated (Box 245)
            DL# 0038e
          - (Mad Extravagant City), undated (Box 245)
            DL# 0039e
          - (Planetarium interior, New York City), undated (Box 245)
            DL# 0040d
          - (Italian coastline, sculpture on cliff), undated (Box 245)
            DL# 0041ab
          - (Lincoln Center, New York City, night), undated (Box 245)
            DL# 0042a
          - The Intrepid, New York City, 1986 (Box 245)
            DL# 0043b
          - (The Intrepid, New York City, close-up), 1986 (Box 245)
            DL# 0044d
          - Cafe Blase, Provincetown, 1990 (Box 245)
            DL# 0045d
          - Convention Center, New York City, 1986 (Box 245)
            DL# 0046d
          - House of Ice, Syracuse, NY, 1985 (Box 245)
            DL# 0047d
      - Ellis Island
        - (wrought iron scrolling vine with note attached) - split toned, 1989 (Box 246)
          EI# 0001a
        - Fumigating Ovens, 1989 (Box 246)
          EI# 0002b
        - File Cabinets - split toned, 1989 (Box 246)
          EI# 0003a
        - Portico, 1989 (Box 246)
          EI# 0004a
        - Passage, 1989 (Box 246)
          EI# 0005
      - Gay Sites
        - (Homomonuments, Amsterdam), undated (Box 246)
          GS# 0005e
        - The Ghost of Gertrude Stein Visits the Lesbian Herstory Archive, 1988 (Box 246)
          GS# 0006d
        - (parade viewers with two George Segal sculptures), undated (Box 246)
          GS# 0009f
        - (Julius', NYC - man near arched doorway) (Box 246)
          GS# 0010f
        - (Julius' and Three Lives Bookstore, corner of W. 10th St., NYC), undated (Box 246)
          GS# 0011f
        - The New York Public Library at Night (Robert Giard's exhibition banner), 1998 (Box 246)
          GS# 0012
        - (Giard exhibition banner, The New York Public Library), 1998 (Box 246)
          GS# 0013e
        - AIDS Memorial - St. John the Divine, NYC (Box 246)
          GS# 0014
        - (Sheridan Square, George Segal Sculptures, NYC), undated (Box 246)
          GS# 0015d
        - (Stonewall, NYC), undated (Box 246)
          GS# 0016f
        - Grave of Oscar Wilde, 1991 (Box 246)
          GS# 0017d
        - Homage to Charles Ludlam, 1989 (Box 246)
          GS# 0018b
        - (Oscar Wilde's Grave - with flowers), 1991 (Box 246)
          GS# 0019d
        - (car, canal - Amsterdam), undated (Box 246)
          GS# 0100
        - (three people, canal-Amsterdam), undated (Box 246)
          GS# 0101
        - (Homomonuments sign, canal-Amsterdam), undated (Box 246)